

Available from late of June

CONTACT

639293352 manelcolominasruiz@gmail.com

Click on my <u>LinkedIn</u> profile to know more about me.

PERSONAL SKILLS

PROGRAMMING			
CREATIVITY			
TEAMWORK			
COMMUNICATION			
SOCIAL			

LANGUAGES

SPANISH			
ENGLISH			
FRENCH			

MANEL COLOMINAS RUIZ

ACTIVE WORK SEARCH

EDUCATION

RESILIENT LEADERSHIP FREE COURSE (HARVARD UNIVERSITY)

NEGOTIATING SALARY FREE COURSE (HARVARD UNIVERSITY)

DOUBLE DEGREE IN AEROSPACE ENGINEERING SYSTEMS AND NETWORK ENGINEERING (EETAC-UPC) (2021- CURRENT)

BACHILLERATO, TECHNOLOGY (2019-2021)

ESO (2015 - 2019)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CAIXABANK S.A. (AUGUST 2024) - MEETER

Application and activation of credit and debit cards, replacement of lost or stolen cards, management of credit limits, knowledge of financial terms, composition of account numbers, knowledge and contracting of financial products, (loans, mortgages, insurance, investment funds, pension plans), cash operations, ATM operations, buying/selling foreign currency, customer acquisition, knowing customers, issuance and collection checks, bank transfers, managing online banking, returning receipts, issuing financial certificates, opening bank accounts, Verification and updating of information of customers (KYC) and customer service skills.

GESIURIS ASSET MANAGEMENT SGIIC SA (JULY 2024) – FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Develop code in Python, HTML and JavaScript for a web application service with the objective of improving the presentation of information to the user. The application has an interactive interface that allow users to make queries. Using AI and economic data bases, PAPERS reports and other verified economic documents, the application provided precise answers to the queries posed by the user.

HOME PIZZA CF S.L. (2022-2023) - DELIVERY MAN

I was responsible for taking the different products requested from the store to the customer's accommodation, as well as the payment process.

COURSE REVIEW (2019-2021)

Provided tutoring in Mathematics, Technology, and Physics to ESO students, improving their understanding and academic performance.

ABOUT ME

I have a strong background in data analysis, programming and systems optimization, with experience developing academic projects using Python, MATLAB, C, C# and other tools to analyze large volumes of data and generate models to solve complex problems. I have designed algorithmic solutions, with linear programming and genetic algorithms, to optimize systems.

I enjoy working in teams, sharing knowledge and applying my technical skills in collaborative environments to solve diverse problems. I have a strong interest in economic analysis and economic policy research, and I believe that data analysis methods can offer great opportunities for improved decision-making in this area.

I am motivated to apply my technical knowledge and my passion in research environments, where I can contribute to the creation of innovative solutions and the optimization of systems.

APTITUDES

- Strategist: Expert in developing and creating strategies to obtain the optimal solution in the most efficient way, with the aim of maximizing profits.
- **Deduction:** Expert in deducing and perceiving information from the environment to reach meaningful and precise conclusions.
- **Motivational:** Skilled in inspiring and motivating others through interpersonal communication, leading teams with a professional approach to members, fostering a collaborative, positive and productive work environment.
- **Troubleshooting:** Skilled in critically analyzing problems and identifying effective solutions. Ability to approach complex problems in a challenging manner and find innovative and efficient solutions.
- **Creativity:** I have an innovative and creative mind, capable of generating original ideas and finding solutions to complex problems. It motivates me to discover other perspectives and approach challenges from a different point of view.
- **Teamwork:** Able to collaborate effectively with multidisciplinary teams to efficiently achieve group goals.
- **Autonomy:** Ability to work independently with a strong disciplined work ethic to achieve my goals.
- **Analytical Thinking:** Able to break down problems into their essential components and analyze their data to draw conclusions. I have skills in interpreting quantitative and qualitative data which help me to strengthen my decision making.

KNOWLEDGES

- DATA ANALYSIS
- AERONAUTICAL
- NETWORK ENGINEERING
- ADVANCED CALCULUS
- ATM (AIR TRAFFIC MANAGEMENT)
- PROGRAMMING (C#, PYTHON, MATLAB, JAVASCRITP, C)
- WORD, EXCEL, POWER POINT
- FLIGHT MECHANICS
- INTERNET PROTOCOLS (TCP, IP, RIP, VLANS, BGP, OSPF, SECURITY FIREWALLS, WIFI, DNS, VOIP, LINUX/WINDOWS.
- FLUID MECHANICS
- AERODYNAMICS
- ELECTRONICS
- SIGNAL PROCESSING
- COMUNICATIONS
- NETWORK ANALYSIS

OFFICIAL LANGUAGE CERTIFICATES

- DELPH B2 FRENCH (2021)
- DELPH B1 FRENCH (2019)
- ENGLISH B2 Not Officially Certified